Robert Smith

System Architect

Phone (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume

Address: 1737 Marshville Road, Alabama

SUMMARY

Eight years of experience in area of IT, those 2 years with management positions. Leadership spirit in development of projects with objective of obtaining better productivity without losing quality. Design to delivery of technology / security business solutions. Linux systems Engineering are main interests.

SKILLS

.

WORK EXPERIENCE

System Architect

NBP - December 2011 - 2020

- Managing Core Banking Servers IBM Power Blade servers, IBM Power 740 Express server, HP superdome2, HP Blade Servers Dell Servers, Specially Managing IBM Storage Servers.
- Maintaining Unix Linux Base Server for smooth functioning core Banking application.
- Integral part implementing FIS Global (profile core banking application) highly available HP superdome2 server.
- Supply essential instructions user maintenance procedures suitable for all functions LAN users.
- · Provide useful software installation up-gradation.
- Implemented and executed an on-line curriculum for reducing data entry errors.

System Architect

Delta Corporation - 2010 - 2011

- Built global country VoIP network in 21 countries.
- Billing and Trouble Ticketing Software, Prov-IV.
- application to feed PA State Trauma compliance software.
- System Architect Full Design, development, testing and implementation using ERwin, Oracle 8i, SQLForms 6.0, Crystal Reports 8 Developer 2000.
- Extensive ETL/Data migration/Data cleansing/QA algorithms developed.(DBA) Design and configuration of rule based data conversion engine for .
- Sep 2000- Apr 2001) York Hospital, Southern PA.
- Provided detailed Systems and Environmental Designs for new back office environment for Operations personnel.

EDUCATION

Master Of Information Technology - 2008(Dadabhoy Institute)